<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Washington DC Photographer Blog &#124; Charlotte Geary Photography</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 15:24:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>

	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=2.8</generator>
	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
			<item>
		<title>Daniel&#8217;s birth story</title>

		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/02/05/daniels-birth-story/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/02/05/daniels-birth-story/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[portraits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[birth photography]]></category>

		<category><![CDATA[births]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[my family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/02/05/daniels-birth-story/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Daniel&#8217;s first cry
January 9, 2011
Mike took some beautiful photos of our son&#8217;s first moments, and I&#8217;m excited to share them with you. Here is Daniel&#8217;s birth story.

Daniel was due on January 3rd, and he was late. On Friday, January 7th, I woke up to mild contractions.  They were irregular and not too uncomfortable, and [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250215_VYssQ-O.jpg"><br />
Daniel&#8217;s first cry<br />
January 9, 2011</p>
<p>Mike took some beautiful photos of our son&#8217;s first moments, and I&#8217;m excited to share them with you. Here is Daniel&#8217;s birth story.</p>
<p><span id="more-1999"></span><br />
Daniel was due on January 3rd, and he was late. On Friday, January 7th, I woke up to mild contractions.  They were irregular and not too uncomfortable, and continued off and on all day Friday and Saturday. Saturday night, I got about an hour of sleep before the contractions got too intense.  By 3am, they were about 4-5 minutes apart and I was whimpering from the pain.  We called the doctor at 3:15am and she told us it was time to go to the hospital.  </p>
<p>We arrived at the hospital at 3:45am on Sunday, January 9th, 2011.  I’d expected to be in complete agony during the car ride to the hospital, but I was calm and kept my sense of humor during that nighttime ride.  Even Mike commented on how relaxed I was.  The pain wasn’t nearly as bad as I’d expected, and I tried not to be nervous. </p>
<p>In triage, they connected me to the monitor and couldn’t detect any of my contractions.  I was so frustrated about that!  The contractions were getting more painful, especially in my lower back, and they couldn’t see a thing on the monitor. It got worse as the nurse made me lie in a painful position that hurt my back so much that I was near tears.  That time was the most pain that I felt during the entire labor and delivery process.  I expected it would just keep getting worse, but I didn’t know that I was already surviving the hardest part of the day. </p>
<p>We were in triage for at least an hour before the nurse called my doctor.  I was scared that they’d send me home, saying that real labor hadn’t begun yet, even though I knew that it had.  I was so relieved when the nurse came back to us and said that the doctor wanted me to stay.  I was 41 weeks pregnant, three centimeters dilated, and if I said I was having contractions, she believed me.  It was time for me to have a baby.  </p>
<p>They admitted us to our own labor and delivery room around 5am.  Eventually the nurses figured out that I was having back labor, which is why the monitor on my upper abdomen couldn&#8217;t detect the contractions. They gave me a different kind of monitor, and sure enough, my contractions were escalating.  </p>
<p>At 7:30am, I asked for the anesthesiologist. He arrived quickly, and was reassuring and kept me calm.  I sat up and followed his directions, but I was terrified about having that needle injected into my spine.  Mike sat in front of me, held my hand, and said all the right things.  He was a wonderful partner throughout the day, and I especially appreciated how he kept me so calm during the epidural.  The insertion of the epidural took about five minutes, and it wasn’t bad at all.  I was a little worried that the epidural might go wrong, but within a few minutes, I started to feel fantastic.  The anxiety was gone, and I just felt relaxed and happy, almost drunk.  </p>
<p>I lay in that bed on my back, propped slightly on one side by pillows and blankets, for the next six hours.  I enjoyed that time of rest, and didn’t even feel bored as I lay peacefully in the bed.  I was completely chilled out and happy.  I watched the monitor to see the intensity and frequency of my contractions increasing, but I couldn’t feel any of it.  Occasionally I’d feel my stomach tightening as I contracted, but there was no pain.  I could move my legs and feel people touch them – basically I could feel everything except for discomfort.  Epidurals are wonders of science!</p>
<p>Around 1:00pm, a friendly nurse came in to chat with us for a while.  All the while, unknown to me, I was in transition, which is considered one of the most difficult parts of labor.  I had just spent spent transition chatting leisurely with a nurse about travel in Australia. At 1:45, the doctor checked my cervix and announced with surprise that I was at least 8cm and dilating quickly!  She said it was time to push.  I was shocked.</p>
<p>Pushing wasn’t nearly as difficult as I expected, and I&#8217;m shocked to say that I actually enjoyed it.  I was feeling no pain, only pressure.  Mike held one of my legs and cradled my head with every push.  I watched the whole process with a mirror, and I think that mirror really helped me focus and recognize successful pushes. Because I had no pain, I was alert, happy, and excited to meet the baby.  Mike was calm and cheerful, despite having every reason to be squeamish instead.  He was wonderful throughout the whole labor and delivery process.</p>
<p>At 2:13pm, after half an hour of pushing, Daniel’s head appeared.  With one more push, he was entirely out.  Mike and I were stunned to see him. I don’t even know if I could describe the how I felt at that moment. Happiness? Relief? Pride? Disbelief? Shock? Elation? Love at first sight? When they put the baby in my arms, I was overcome with the most intense joy I could ever imagine. I wept. He was finally here. Life doesn&#8217;t get any better than this.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250242_8drCH-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250244_VXF7F-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250231_aYtgt-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250224_dEL9p-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250220_ZNMom-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250210_4T4QS-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250205_LGZa9-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250200_Yir74-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250194_FDDjp-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250188_oewTt-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250186_KCN6m-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1177250180_ea8pB-O.jpg"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/02/05/daniels-birth-story/feed/</wfw:commentRss>

		<slash:comments>32</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maternity leave</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/02/01/maternity-leave/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/02/01/maternity-leave/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 02:55:16 +0000</pubDate>

		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/?p=1994</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We finally moved into our new house last weekend, and we&#8217;re absolutely loving it.  With a three-week-old baby and a house full of unpacked boxes, I will continue to take time away from the office for a while.  I will be needing extra time to respond to emails and voice messages over the [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We finally moved into our new house last weekend, and we&#8217;re absolutely loving it.  With a three-week-old baby and a house full of unpacked boxes, I will continue to take time away from the office for a while.  <b>I will be needing extra time to respond to emails and voice messages over the next several weeks</b>. In the meanwhile, I&#8217;m loving this time with my family as we settle into our new home and continue to fall in love with little Daniel.  Thanks for all your support, everyone!</p>
<p>Stay tuned for baby photos &#8211; I promise that they&#8217;re coming!  I just haven&#8217;t had time to process them yet, but I hope to have several to share very soon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/02/01/maternity-leave/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>

		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our other big news: Hello, Reston!</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/20/our-other-big-news-hello-reston/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/20/our-other-big-news-hello-reston/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>

				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[my family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/20/our-other-big-news-hello-reston/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Our new neighborhood
Reston, Virginia
If having a baby wasn&#8217;t enough excitement for one week, we also bought a house last week!  We left Colorado on November 1st, and it has taken us all this time to find a house that is perfect for us.  My wonderful parents invited us to stay with them during [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1160759600_TAZoW-O.jpg"><br />
Our new neighborhood<br />
Reston, Virginia</p>
<p>If having a baby wasn&#8217;t enough excitement for one week, we also bought a house last week!  We left Colorado on November 1st, and it has taken us all this time to find a house that is perfect for us.  My wonderful parents invited us to stay with them during the months that we were house hunting. We had a hard time finding houses that we liked within our budget in neighborhoods that appeal to us, so we took our time.</p>
<p>Finally we discovered a gorgeous, mid-century modern house in Reston, Virginia. This house was beautiful indoors, but we also fell in love with the lake scenery and walkable community.  The house is just a few minutes&#8217; walk away from restaurants, shops, salons, art galleries, a coffee shop, a post office, a pool, and offices.  The lake itself surrounds us with the natural beauty that we loved about our Colorado home.  In short, it&#8217;s our dream house.  We didn&#8217;t think we&#8217;d find a house that we love even half as much.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ll be spending the next few weeks moving in.  Having a new baby and a new house at the same time is going to keep us BUSY.  I&#8217;m taking maternity leave right now, but I understand that wedding planning can&#8217;t always wait for new mothers.  I apologize for the extra time I need right now for responding to emails and phone calls, and I hope you understand.  Email is the best way to reach me in the next couple weeks.</p>
<p>After we get settled in the new house, I&#8217;ll be meeting with clients there.  I can&#8217;t wait!  I&#8217;m especially excited to have friends and family over in the warmer months for drinks on the patio and canoe trips on the lake.  I&#8217;m so excited that I can&#8217;t believe it&#8217;s not too good to be true.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/20/our-other-big-news-hello-reston/feed/</wfw:commentRss>

		<slash:comments>17</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The new addition to our family</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/18/the-new-addition-to-our-family/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/18/the-new-addition-to-our-family/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>

		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[my family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/18/the-new-addition-to-our-family/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Daniel, age one week
Dreaming of milk and cuddles
Here&#8217;s our beautiful little boy!  Daniel is one week old now, and is the sweetest thing I&#8217;ve ever seen.  He&#8217;s quiet, content, and very snuggly. I&#8217;ve been so busy that I haven&#8217;t had a chance to process or post his pictures yet, so here are a [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1160759646_JU8ES-O.jpg"><br />
Daniel, age one week<br />
Dreaming of milk and cuddles</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s our beautiful little boy!  Daniel is one week old now, and is the sweetest thing I&#8217;ve ever seen.  He&#8217;s quiet, content, and very snuggly. I&#8217;ve been so busy that I haven&#8217;t had a chance to process or post his pictures yet, so here are a few quick ones from the weekend.  Soon I&#8217;ll share the photos of his first week, including some from his birth.  Mike and I are so happy and completely infatuated with the little guy already!</p>
<p><span id="more-1989"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1160759616_Gtthi-O.jpg"><br />
Sitting on the staircase in our new house.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1160759608_e4wSb-O.jpg"><br />
Ally has been so sweet and gentle around the baby!</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1160759623_txkt4-O.jpg"><br />
I love being his mother.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/18/the-new-addition-to-our-family/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>49</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>He&#8217;s here!</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/10/hes-here/</link>

		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/10/hes-here/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 02:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[my family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[via iphone]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/10/hes-here/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Welcome to the world, Daniel Anthony Pritchard! He was born Sunday, January 9th, weighing 7 pounds 10 ounces. He&#8217;s adorable, healthy, and very cuddly. Mike took this picture just minutes after he was born, when I held Danny for the first time. We are already smitten with our little blond cherub.

Yesterday was Daniel&#8217;s birthday, and [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pics.livejournal.com/charlottegeary/pic/000045s7" height="550" alt="" /></p>
<p>Welcome to the world, Daniel Anthony Pritchard! He was born Sunday, January 9th, weighing 7 pounds 10 ounces. He&#8217;s adorable, healthy, and very cuddly. Mike took this picture just minutes after he was born, when I held Danny for the first time. We are already smitten with our little blond cherub.</p>
<p><img src="http://pics.livejournal.com/charlottegeary/pic/000050rw" height="550" alt="" /></p>
<p>Yesterday was Daniel&#8217;s birthday, and today is Mike&#8217;s. My family had a birthday party for the two of them tonight in my hospital room, where they took this picture of us. Happy birthday to both of my beloved men!</p>
<p>I&#8217;m updating my blog from the hospital with my cell phone, so I can only post my iPhone pictures at this point. I will share the real photos after I get home and settled. In the meanwhile, I&#8217;m resting comfortably and loving all the cuddles with the baby.</p>
<p>Mike and I are so touched by the outpouring of love and support from all our friends near and far. Thank you for cheering for us &#8211; every message has been cherished.</p>
<p><em><small>Posted via <a href="http://community.livejournal.com/cosysoftware_en/">LiveJournal.app</a>.</small></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/10/hes-here/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>123</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>

		<title>Tips for Shooting Weddings While Pregnant</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/06/tips-for-shooting-weddings-while-pregnant/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/06/tips-for-shooting-weddings-while-pregnant/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 22:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>

		<category><![CDATA[photo tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tips for photographers]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/06/tips-for-shooting-weddings-while-pregnant/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
My official due date of January 3rd has come and gone, so we&#8217;re officially on Baby Watch 2011 around here.  He could come any day now, so stay tuned for our exciting news!  I&#8217;ll update my blogs with baby photos as soon as I can, and I&#8217;ll be keeping my Facebook and Twitter [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1037340845_Zwb2x-L.jpg"></p>
<p>My official due date of January 3rd has come and gone, so we&#8217;re officially on Baby Watch 2011 around here.  He could come any day now, so stay tuned for our exciting news!  I&#8217;ll update my blogs with baby photos as soon as I can, and I&#8217;ll be keeping my <a target="_blank" href="http://www.facebook.com/charlotte.geary">Facebook</a> and <a target="_blank" href="http://twitter.com/charlottegeary">Twitter</a> accounts updated as we go. <img src='http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif' alt=':)' class='wp-smiley' /> </p>
<p>In the meanwhile, I thought I&#8217;d share a few things that I&#8217;ve learned this year about how to photograph weddings while pregnant.  I know that I was nervous about how to handle a pregnancy with my hectic and physically demanding career, and I would have loved to have someone offer me tips before I got started.  So if you are a wedding photographer who is planning to have a baby soon, here&#8217;s some advice to help you out.</p>
<p><b>Before you get pregnant</b></p>
<p><i>1. Get in shape. </i><br />
Shooting weddings requires strength and endurance under normal conditions, so if you gain 25 pounds of awkwardly-distributed baby weight, you&#8217;ll need to be very fit to handle an eight-hour wedding shoot. Thanks to Weight Watchers and frequent workouts, I lost 13 pounds before getting pregnant. By the time wedding season came along, I was strong enough to trek around steep mountain venues at 11,000 feet of altitude.  </p>
<p><i>2. Try to schedule your pregnancy around wedding season.</i><br />
Timing a pregnancy is very difficult for most people, but if you can, consider your wedding schedule while planning your pregnancy.  I hoped to have a January baby, and amazingly, that worked out just right for us.  My slower spring months took place during my first trimester, when I was at my sickest. By the time my hectic summer months of July, August, and September arrived, I was in my second trimester and feeling much livelier. My last wedding of the year took place in mid-November, when I was 7.5 months along and still very active.  I wouldn&#8217;t have wanted to shoot later than eight months along, because by then I was large, unwieldly, and achy. The baby is due to arrive in January, my slowest month of the year.  I&#8217;ll have a few months of maternity leave before wedding season begins again. </p>
<p><b>Surviving morning sickness</b></p>
<p><i>1. Rely on adrenaline</i><br />
I won&#8217;t sugarcoat it: morning sickness is a lot worse than I&#8217;d expected.  I was sick all day, every day, for about 17 or 18 weeks.  But every weekend I&#8217;d arrive at a wedding and suddenly feel great.  The excitement of the wedding, the stress of the job, and the thrill of loving my work all created a happy buzz that I could only attribute to adrenaline.  Often the only time I felt good was while shooting.  If you find yourself suffering from morning sickness, just dive right into the photo shoot and you&#8217;ll be fine.  Really.</p>
<p><i>2. Bring food and water.</i><br />
I felt sicker when I was hungry.  As soon as hunger pangs hit, I would need to eat immediately.  During my morning sickness months, I brought tons of easily digestible snacks to weddings, such as bagels, oranges, and snack bars. Hydration is also extremely important, because pregnant women need more water than other people. Do not let yourself skip water breaks.</p>
<p><i>3. Rest during the weekdays.</i><br />
Take as many naps and breaks as you can manage when you&#8217;re not shooting. I was lucky enough to have a few hours of productive time per day before I started feeling really sick.  I used those morning hours to get tons of work done before lying down during the rough afternoon hours.  I don&#8217;t know who in their right mind named it &#8220;morning sickness&#8221; &#8212; morning was the only time I felt decent!  </p>
<p><b>Outsource what you can</b></p>
<p><i>1. Hire good help for the wedding days. </i><br />
It&#8217;s risky for a pregnant woman to carry heavy bags, so consider hiring an assistant to do your heavy lifting for you. If you find yourself needing more breaks to rest your feet or use the restroom, make sure that you bring a skilled second shooter to cover those moments.</p>
<p><i>2. Hire help for when you&#8217;re not shooting.</i><br />
Outsource your work during the weekdays, too. If you&#8217;re too tired or sick to spend much time at the computer, outsource your photo processing.  Or hire a bookkeeper.  Or administrative assistant. I decided that I wanted to keep doing my own work for the business, but I hired a house cleaner to take care of the home that I was neglecting.  I loved having someone clean the house while I was napping!</p>
<p><b>If your photographer turns out to be pregnant</b></p>
<p>Please don&#8217;t worry!  I created some of my best work of all time this year, so the pregnancy didn&#8217;t slow me down at all.  Take good care of your pregnant photographer, and offer her lots of water, and everything will be just fine.  </p>
<p>Later this year I plan to share tips on how to photograph your babies, so stay tuned!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2011/01/06/tips-for-shooting-weddings-while-pregnant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>14</slash:comments>

		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wedding albums for Liz and Brian</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/30/wedding-albums-for-liz-and-brian/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/30/wedding-albums-for-liz-and-brian/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>

				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[albums]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coffee table book]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flushmount album]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/30/wedding-albums-for-liz-and-brian/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Now that Christmas has passed, I can share the beautiful albums from Liz and Brian&#8217;s wedding.  They ordered five albums: a 12&#215;12 leather flushmount album for themselves, two 8&#215;8 leather flushmounts for their parents, and two 8&#215;8 leather coffee table books for their grandparents.  I really loved their winter wedding at Donovan Pavilion [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" width="750" alt="Flushmount wedding albums" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751542_HMWce-O.jpg"></p>
<p>Now that Christmas has passed, I can share the beautiful albums from Liz and Brian&#8217;s wedding.  They ordered five albums: a 12&#215;12 leather flushmount album for themselves, two 8&#215;8 leather flushmounts for their parents, and two 8&#215;8 leather coffee table books for their grandparents.  I really loved their <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/03/24/liz-and-brian-vail-winter-wedding-at-the-vail-chapel-and-donovan-pavilion/">winter wedding at Donovan Pavilion in Vail</a>, and the final albums are beautiful.  </p>
<p><span id="more-1967"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" width="750" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751553_MxFmd-O-1.jpg"><br />
Their five albums: three flushmount albums and two coffee table books</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Wedding album box" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751527_nZCAX-O.jpg"><br />
The flushmount albums came in silver boxes with a slight metallic sheen and an inset photo.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Silver wedding album box" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751512_zfxPP-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Black leather wedding albums" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751664_QgjkF-O.jpg"><br />
Liz and Brian chose a black leather cover with a cameo photo for the wedding album and parent albums.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Black leather flushmount wedding album" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751572_PAcNK-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Black leather flushmount wedding album" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751600_yZ2UT-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Flushmount wedding album" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751607_e7yLx-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751621_RCeAa-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751619_TJwUR-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751647_AbsUr-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751653_2K9B6-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Coffee table books with leather cover" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751661_WYb84-O.jpg"><br />
The two coffee table books had charcoal gray leather covers.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Wedding coffee table book" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751673_C4kws-O.jpg"><br />
The coffee table books have hinged pages that lie flat when opened.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="Press printed wedding album" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751692_q6uSo-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="WHCC wedding album" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751708_soGet-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="WHCC press printed book" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751714_UHMs8-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" alt="WHCC coffee table book" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128751725_zMaVn-O.jpg"><br />
Coffee table books make wonderful gifts for grandparents.</p>
]]></content:encoded>

			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/30/wedding-albums-for-liz-and-brian/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>9</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>My favorites of 2010: Portraits</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/28/my-favorites-of-2010-portraits/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/28/my-favorites-of-2010-portraits/#comments</comments>

		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[portraits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[babies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[births]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[couples]]></category>

		<category><![CDATA[engagement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[families]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pets]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/28/my-favorites-of-2010-portraits/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
After posting several of my favorite wedding photos of 2010 last week, I thought I&#8217;d complete the set by including a collection of some of the portraits that I&#8217;ve loved through the year.  2010 gave me an opportunity to photograph engaged couples, families, seniors, and two births.  





Brent and his father, just minutes [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="senior portrait" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691701_PFP7u-O.jpg"></p>
<p>After posting several of <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/21/my-favorites-of-2010-weddings/">my favorite wedding photos of 2010</a> last week, I thought I&#8217;d complete the set by including a collection of some of the portraits that I&#8217;ve loved through the year.  2010 gave me an opportunity to photograph engaged couples, families, seniors, and two births.  </p>
<p><span id="more-1963"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="engagement portrait" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691692_Poib8-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="family portrait" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691677_vWctZ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement portrait" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691667_ujo8w-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="birth photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691657_zmjuJ-O.jpg"><br />
Brent and his father, just minutes after birth</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement portrait photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691656_B8PHp-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="farm photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691643_ECQNA-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691628_YBUCa-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="birth photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691617_xCuHm-O.jpg"><br />
Meeting her daughter for the first time</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="birth photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691610_iSdma-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement portraits" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691618_woGF3-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement pictures" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691596_4DZrn-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="baby photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691587_8VMuh-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement portrait photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691583_xiH67-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="senior photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691574_vE9RW-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691558_b4jsk-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691555_5aiL5-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="family portraits" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691539_PYMWm-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="senior picture photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691532_qXnQJ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691523_JQ6tn-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="dog photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691519_a7prz-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691510_2RHHb-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="family photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691505_Hv8Ld-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement portrait with horses" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691494_CVfui-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement portrait at night" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691486_er3AX-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="baby photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691464_Ei57D-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="senior portrait photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691465_CRrGN-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement portrait at sunset" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691491_7scsZ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="engagement portrait at night" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691436_pLF2x-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="family portrait photographer" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691425_LB8H4-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="cowboy engagement portrait" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691412_aaW3F-O.jpg"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/28/my-favorites-of-2010-portraits/feed/</wfw:commentRss>

		<slash:comments>24</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>My favorites of 2010: Weddings</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/21/my-favorites-of-2010-weddings/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/21/my-favorites-of-2010-weddings/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate>

		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/21/my-favorites-of-2010-weddings/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
It&#8217;s been such a full year for me!  In addition to nine months of pregnancy and a move from Colorado to Virginia, 2010 also marked my busiest photography year so far. I had fun looking back through the year&#8217;s images and choosing some of my favorites.  It was hard to narrow them down, [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="Bride and groom under double rainbow" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691727_LVcmo-O.jpg"></p>
<p>It&#8217;s been such a full year for me!  In addition to nine months of pregnancy and a move from Colorado to Virginia, 2010 also marked my busiest photography year so far. I had fun looking back through the year&#8217;s images and choosing some of my favorites.  It was hard to narrow them down, but here are some of the ones that really stood out to me this year. </p>
<p><span id="more-1958"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691716_Pnbr8-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691705_7xdXp-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Vail interfaith chapel" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691396_nzJbQ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Father-daughter dance" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691388_rYcG2-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Lake Tahoe wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691378_fjnWK-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691373_RK8Nk-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Garden of the Gods" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691359_N5ckp-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691344_ANgjh-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691346_BKkcy-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691332_XVdRE-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691334_kDnXL-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691317_uA2FR-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Donovan Pavilion wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691314_4QcZm-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="St. Audries Park" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691300_ueYHQ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691284_iAPYD-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691278_aPDWJ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691267_DDNVW-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691257_anGmf-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691250_XCarP-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691242_v5F6A-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691235_9NsLG-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691231_TteUL-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691223_tWs5c-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691208_tiFjC-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="467" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691199_H4xBB-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="467" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691194_76ZzG-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691192_aLZfd-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691164_STyUE-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691143_daumb-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691121_UdUdT-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691054_jakrL-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691030_LczWV-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691031_VVK22-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691025_vQ6tP-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691026_jcU4m-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691028_fhb2Q-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691033_fBXUm-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691027_LTQ6h-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691038_7TJ7o-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691032_GrFgV-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1133691029_gZbmB-O.jpg"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/21/my-favorites-of-2010-weddings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>

		<slash:comments>41</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>38 weeks pregnant</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/19/38-weeks-pregnant/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/19/38-weeks-pregnant/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>

		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[my family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/19/38-weeks-pregnant/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Mike + me + 1
December 19, 2010
Today I&#8217;m 38 weeks pregnant!  The baby is full term, and we&#8217;re just waiting for him to make his debut.  The pregnancy has been going well, and the baby seems to be doing great. I feel fine and I&#8217;m reasonably active these days, but I do have [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="38 weeks pregnant" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1131690371_zxy7d-O.jpg"><br />
Mike + me + 1<br />
December 19, 2010</p>
<p>Today I&#8217;m 38 weeks pregnant!  The baby is full term, and we&#8217;re just waiting for him to make his debut.  The pregnancy has been going well, and the baby seems to be doing great. I feel fine and I&#8217;m reasonably active these days, but I do have more backaches and insomnia than ever.  I think we have just about everything prepared for the little guy&#8217;s arrival, so at this point, we&#8217;re just waiting.  I&#8217;m excited and trying not to get nervous!</p>
<p>Today my mother took some pictures of Mike and me and the baby bump.  Thanks, Mom! </p>
<p><span id="more-1956"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="38 weeks pregnant" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1131690354_BJbsP-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1131690364_pm7HM-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="38 weeks pregnant" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1131690327_e4rks-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="38 weeks pregnant" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1131690315_BL4UB-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="38 weeks pregnant" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1131690307_FF43M-O.jpg"></p>
]]></content:encoded>

			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/19/38-weeks-pregnant/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>39</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>My favorites of 2010: Creative wedding details</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/16/creative-wedding-details-my-favorites-of-2010/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/16/creative-wedding-details-my-favorites-of-2010/#comments</comments>

		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 01:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wedding ideas]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/16/creative-wedding-details-my-favorites-of-2010/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Wedding bouquet made of heirloom brooches
I saw such clever and beautiful wedding details this year!  I thought it would be fun to highlight some of my favorites of 2010 in a blog post.  Here are some of the most interesting decorations, flowers, accessories, and food that I saw at weddings this year!


At a [...]]]></description>

			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="Wedding bouquet made of jewelry" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769379_jPy9A-O-3.jpg"><br />
Wedding bouquet made of heirloom brooches</p>
<p>I saw such clever and beautiful wedding details this year!  I thought it would be fun to highlight some of my favorites of 2010 in a blog post.  Here are some of the most interesting decorations, flowers, accessories, and food that I saw at weddings this year!</p>
<p><span id="more-1950"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="Wedding guestbook skis" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769381_kCqHs-O.jpg"><br />
At a winter wedding in Vail, guests signed these antique skis instead of a traditional guestbook.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Photo tied around bridal bouquet" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769393_xittg-O.jpg"><br />
A locket with a photo of the bride&#8217;s grandparents was tied around the base of her bouquet.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Lavender wedding placecards" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769401_WJxDP-O.jpg"><br />
Bundles of dried lavender accompanied each place card. </p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Hot chocolate bar" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769410_2BoLq-O.jpg"><br />
A hot chocolate buffet was a cozy touch for a winter wedding reception.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Personalized wedding Converse sneakers" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769420_PEdtb-O.jpg"><br />
The bride wore Converse sneakers that were personalized with her new married name.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Lego cake topper" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769426_j9pVp-O.jpg"><br />
This cake was topped with a Lego version of the bride and groom.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Pink ribbon on bridal bouquet" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769434_UQbkC-O.jpg"><br />
This bridal bouquet was fastened with beautifully laced pink ribbons. </p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Potted herbs as wedding favors" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769438_wtWit-O.jpg"><br />
This bride and groom grew potted herbs to give away as wedding favors.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Simpsons donut cake" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769453_DYgAk-O.jpg"><br />
The groom was surprised with a Simpsons donut groom&#8217;s cake.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Purple wedding shoes" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769471_m23iF-O.jpg"><br />
Of course I loved these purple Kate Spade wedding shoes.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Homemade wedding cupcakes" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769477_fGeDN-O.jpg"><br />
This bride is a baker who put an apron over her gown, and decorated wedding cupcakes before the ceremony.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Names carved in bark for centerpiece" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769487_9iTae-O.jpg"><br />
This centerpiece sat in a pot covered with aspen bark carved with the bride&#8217;s and groom&#8217;s initials.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Love bird reception theme" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769495_nzdpx-O.jpg"><br />
A love bird theme offered many cute touches at this reception.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Blue wedding jewelry" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769502_enCcU-O.jpg"><br />
These blue earrings were a perfect match for the bride&#8217;s eyes.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Ski wedding cake topper" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769513_NgvSx-O.jpg"><br />
The cake was topped with snow crystals, with the bride and groom skiing down the hill.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Postcard wedding guestbook" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769517_iNFA9-O.jpg"><br />
Instead of a guestbook, guests wrote messages and drew pictures on postcards. </p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Wedding rosary" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769523_BfUX5-O.jpg"><br />
This bride carried her grandmother&#8217;s rosary.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Chocolate covered strawberry cake topper" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769527_x5vjP-O.jpg"><br />
Chocolate covered strawberries dressed like a groom and bride topped this chocolate wedding cake.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Diamond wedding ring" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769536_8U2wU-O.jpg"><br />
This diamond was set so that it was open on the sides and bottom. </p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Silver Louboutin wedding shoes" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769543_2657Q-O.jpg"><br />
Silver Louboutin wedding shoes added some drama to this bride&#8217;s ensemble.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Pumpkin ring pillow" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769550_5qL4c-O.jpg"><br />
Instead of a traditional ring pillow, the ring bearer carried rings fastened to a pumpkin at this October wedding.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Pine cone groom's boutonniere" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769561_cjmj5-O.jpg"><br />
A hint of pine cone was a beautiful Colorado touch for this groom&#8217;s boutonniere.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Birdcage veil and hat" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769566_3tMfm-O.jpg"><br />
This stylish bride wore a hat with a birdcage veil.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Brown and red wedding cake" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769574_Yxdzs-O.jpg"><br />
This five-tier wedding cake was the perfect touch of elegance for this log cabin mountain wedding.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Green wedding shoes" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769579_mFA2e-O.jpg"><br />
These colorful green shoes added a subtle touch of color for the bride.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Bridesmaid with purple dress and orange flowers" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769586_FGWcn-O.jpg"><br />
This color combination of purple, orange, and green was a gorgeous touch for a fall wedding.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Halloween wedding favor" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769597_icaS2-O.jpg"><br />
Guests at this October wedding received bags of Halloween goodies as their wedding favors.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Virginia Tech groom's cake" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769605_gTjdg-O.jpg"><br />
Instead of a groom&#8217;s cake, this wedding offered chocolate cupcakes honoring the groom&#8217;s alma mater of Virginia Tech.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Personalized wedding champagne flutes" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769610_JqDXF-O.jpg"><br />
The bride and groom&#8217;s new initials were etched into these champagne flutes.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Dogs at wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769622_9zZfj-O.jpg"><br />
These dogs got dressed up for the occasion.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Sangria at wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769642_mJdq4-O.jpg"><br />
Homemade sangria was a hit at this wedding reception.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Antique Mustang at wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769646_cXkA2-O.jpg"><br />
This bride and groom left their ceremony in an antique Mustang.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Grilled cheese snacks at wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769658_YWd46-O.jpg"><br />
After a few hours of dancing, these guests were offered platters of grilled cheese sandwiches as late night snacks.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Cookie wedding cake" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769666_xpvmh-O.jpg"><br />
Instead of a wedding cake, this bride and groom served a tower of cookies, which was displayed next to a drawing of one of their engagement portraits.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Cowboy theme wedding placecards" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769676_xueg2-O.jpg"><br />
These cowboy place cards greeted guests at a Texas-themed wedding rehearsal dinner.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Place cards hung from tree" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769679_3UsSu-O.jpg"><br />
These place cards were hung from branches with ribbons.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Wedding gelato bar" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769688_ey5nH-O.jpg"><br />
A gelato bar was a fun substitute for traditional wedding desserts. </p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Outdoor urban wedding reception" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769689_ctvdR-O.jpg"><br />
The bride and groom hosted their guests in an outdoor, urban wedding reception under the stars.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Fireworks at wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1128769696_mWvWK-O.jpg"><br />
A cuddle under fireworks was the perfect ending for this wedding day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/16/creative-wedding-details-my-favorites-of-2010/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>21</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selecting photos for your wedding album</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/14/selecting-photos-for-your-wedding-album/</link>

		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/14/selecting-photos-for-your-wedding-album/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[albums]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[for photographers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tips for brides]]></category>

		<category><![CDATA[tips for photographers]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/15/selecting-photos-for-your-wedding-album/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Now that it is a busy time of year for wedding album design, I thought I&#8217;d offer some tips for brides and grooms who are selecting photos for their albums.  It can be difficult to choose the right pictures, especially when you can&#8217;t visualize how they will all go together in the book.  [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now that it is a busy time of year for wedding album design, I thought I&#8217;d offer some tips for brides and grooms who are selecting photos for their albums.  It can be difficult to choose the right pictures, especially when you can&#8217;t visualize how they will all go together in the book.  </p>
<p>Because your photographer is experienced in album design, he or she will know what sorts of photographs to include.  If you have any concerns about the selection process, <b>I urge you to have your photographer select the photos</b>.  I offer my clients a choice: they can choose all the photos, or I can do it.  After I design a first draft of an album, my clients can request any changes, so they always have total control over the photos that go in the final book.  </p>
<p><b>If you&#8217;d like to choose the photos for your book, here are some tips to follow:</b><br />
1. Start with a cover image that is meaningful and appropriate.<br />
2. Choose a photo that would make a great opening image on page 1.<br />
3. Include several photos of the details.<br />
4. Include photos that show both action and reaction.<br />
5. Be consistent with photos of family within the flow of events.<br />
6. Don&#8217;t choose a photo that won&#8217;t fit with any other pictures.<br />
7. Trust your photographer&#8217;s judgment about color vs. black and white.<br />
8. End the story with a closing photo for the last page.</p>
<p><span id="more-1934"></span></p>
<h2>1. Start with a cover image that is meaningful and appropriate. </h2>
<p>If your album will have a photo on the cover, don&#8217;t forget to specify which photo you want to be there.  I recommend that you choose a portrait of the two of you, but some candid moments work well, too.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipscover02/1126956719_DVACN-O.jpg"><br />
If your cover will have a small inset photo, the best choices are simple images that will look good in a small size. Make sure the colors in the photo will look good with the color that you&#8217;ve chosen for the cover material.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipscover01/1126956706_2R2AD-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipscover03/1126956722_d2bnZ-O.jpg"><br />
If your album will have a full photo cover, you can choose an image with more detail, because it will be larger and easier to see.  </p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipscover04/1126956728_TvR82-O.jpg"></p>
<h2>2. Choose a photo that would make a great opening image on page 1. </h2>
<p>Your album needs an opening page that serves as an introduction to the wedding day.  This first page may also be a title page, depending on the layout style of your book.  Make sure that you select a photo (or photos) that will get your story off to a good start.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsopening01/1126956810_dxd8c-O.jpg"><br />
If your wedding took place in a scenic location, a landscape photo will be a great way to introduce the setting.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsopening02/1126956853_VGRkS-O.jpg"><br />
A photo of the venue is also a good scene-setter for the first page.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsopening03/1126956858_wno7o-O.jpg"><br />
You can also begin with a photo of the invitation and/or rings, as an introduction to the events of the day.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsopening04/1126956875_rLanB-O.jpg"><br />
A portrait of the two of you also makes for a great opening page, if you don&#8217;t mind that it will be out of chronological order from the rest of the book.</p>
<h2>3. Include several photos of the details.</h2>
<p>Detail photos reveal a lot of information about the theme, mood, and appearance of your wedding day. Be sure to select related sets of detail pictures, so they can be grouped together in the book.  If you choose one picture of a bouquet or centerpiece, and no other details, it&#8217;s difficult to find a place to put those pictures within the album. </p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsdetails01/1126956765_VMMVc-O.jpg"><br />
I like to start with getting-ready details before the ceremony.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsdetails02/1126956751_LB3bR-O.jpg"><br />
A layout of ceremony details is a great way to introduce that part of the day.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsdetails03/1126956761_dHfpE-O.jpg"><br />
Some of the most beautiful details are found at the reception, so be sure to include several of those photos.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsdetails04/1126956791_iTpPa-O.jpg"></p>
<h2>4. Include photos that show both action and reaction.</h2>
<p>  This is also my philosophy when taking photographs. The story is best told by documenting the main events that occur, along with people&#8217;s reactions to those events. It&#8217;s worth the cost of extra album photos to tell the complete story.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsactionreaction01/1126956537_PapHy-O.jpg"><br />
When the groom sees the bride for the first time, be sure to include pictures of her arrival as well as the look on his face when he sees her.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsactionreaction02/1126956548_HvyiB-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsactionreaction03/1126956560_4BaFa-O.jpg"><br />
During the toasts, be sure to include not only the speakers, but also the people laughing or crying in response.  By looking at these example photos, you can tell that the speeches were hilarious, which gives a lot of information about the story of the day.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsactionreaction04/1126956593_GaREh-O.jpg"><br />
Instead of showing only the father-daughter dance and the mother-son dance, include a photo of the bride&#8217;s mother crying as she watches.  Her tears reveal a lot about the closeness of their family.</p>
<h2>5. Be consistent with photos of family within the flow of events.</h2>
<p> Try to choose a fairly even mix of pictures of both sides of the family, but keep consistent with the major events of the day. <b>The most common mistake I see in photo selection is that people choose photos of family that don&#8217;t fit into the events of the day.</b>  Lots of my clients will count photos of their family and try to keep that equal, instead of considering how those photos will fit into the album.  (For example, &#8220;I have four photos of my mom, and four photos of his mom in the book.  So it&#8217;s equal.&#8221;)  But make sure that you choose the right timing of the day to keep these photos truly equivalent.  </p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsconsistency04/1126956691_DKtsW-O.jpg"><br />
For example, if you include a picture of the father-daughter dance, definitely include one of the mother-son dance. Often people will omit one or the other, choosing instead to use a different photo of their parent later in the reception. Although that might seem equal when you are counting photos of individual people (&#8221;four photos of mom&#8221;), it doesn&#8217;t make sense because you have eliminated an important event in the day.  Showing the father-daughter dance without the mother-son dance is not an equal distribution of family photos, no matter what the overall count may be.  </p>
<p>My advice: Don&#8217;t count photos of people. Include important moments and tell the story. </p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsconsistency03/1126956684_f4iDS-O.jpg"><br />
The same concept applies to other events of the day.  For example, if three people give speeches, include photos of all three of them. Even if there is a better photo of your best man from a different part of the day, don&#8217;t leave him out of the speech photos.  He worked hard on that toast.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsconsistency01/1126956655_dyPwk-O.jpg"><br />
When choosing family formals, be consistent between families.  In this example, each page shows a photo of the bride or groom with the parents, and then a full family photo with siblings.  It doesn&#8217;t matter which formals you want to include, but do make them consistent between families.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsconsistency02/1126956682_PaG2F-O.jpg"><br />
In this example of wedding party photos, the bride and groom selected a relaxed group picture of the ladies, and then a similarly relaxed one of the guys laughing.  Be consistent between groups.</p>
<h2>6. Don&#8217;t choose a photo that won&#8217;t fit with any other pictures.</h2>
<p>  <b>Another common mistake that I see are pictures that aren&#8217;t chosen as part of a group of related images.</b>  For example, if you choose several photos of the ladies getting ready, and only one of the guys getting ready, it will have to go on its own page by itself. That one photo won&#8217;t belong with any others in the book.</p>
<p>I often see people choosing one candid photo that occurs during the formal portraits.  Those pictures are especially difficult to fit in the book.  Typically the pages before the formals are the ceremony, and the pages after the formals are the portraits of the bride and groom.  If there is one picture of a bridesmaid laughing during the formals, I don&#8217;t know where to put it.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsformals01/1126956784_BuBL6-O.jpg"><br />
This is pretty typical for a layout of family formals.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsformals02/1126956796_Xnhg7-O.jpg"><br />
Here&#8217;s another example of formals.  If there is a laughing bridesmaid photo that needs to go in there somewhere, it just doesn&#8217;t fit.</p>
<h2>7. Trust your photographer&#8217;s judgment about color vs. black and white.</h2>
<p>  It&#8217;s not desirable to mix color and b/w photos on the same page, because it&#8217;s distracting to the eye and doesn&#8217;t flow together well.  If your photographer wants to have a page that is all black and white, it is probably done with very good reason. </p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsbw01/1126956576_fUotr-O.jpg"><br />
The photo on the right was originally color, but it looks much better in this layout as black and white.  Don&#8217;t be alarmed if your photographer changes it for the sake of the album. </p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsbw03/1126956594_MU5UC-O.jpg"><br />
This series of images is much more impactful with a consistent b/w treatment and layout. </p>
<h2>8. End the story with a closing photo for the last page.</h2>
<p>  Think of how you want the book to end, and be sure to include a photo for that purpose.  </p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsclosing02/1126956609_mw6di-L.jpg"><br />
A relaxed candid or portrait of the two of you at the end of the night is a great choice.</p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsclosing03/1126956625_bnxDS-O.jpg"><br />
Your rings can be a nice closing image. </p>
<p><img border="1" width="750" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/Albums/Album-photo-selection-examples/AlbumTipsclosing01/1126956599_5tvA8-O.jpg"><br />
Sunset over your venue is a clear way to show the ending of the day.</p>
<h2>The most important things to remember:</h2>
<p><b>1. Your album is a book that tells a story.</b><br />
Select photos that include the important moments and tell the complete story. </p>
<p><b>2. Your album is an art piece.</b><br />
Select photos that you find beautiful.</p>
<p><b>3. Your album is a family heirloom.</b><br />
Select photos that will be important to you and your family and your future generations.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/14/selecting-photos-for-your-wedding-album/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>20</slash:comments>
		</item>

		<item>
		<title>The last colors of fall</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/06/the-last-colors-of-fall/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/06/the-last-colors-of-fall/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>

				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virginia]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/06/the-last-colors-of-fall/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Early December is technically still autumn, but it always felt like winter in Colorado. Here in Virginia there are still a few colorful leaves on the trees, mostly due to the gorgeous Japanese maples that are sprinkled throughout town. This one in my parents&#8217; front yard keeps me craving pumpkin soup and apple cider. Its [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="Japanese maple" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1110209498_CYXzh-O.jpg"></p>
<p>Early December is technically still autumn, but it always felt like winter in Colorado. Here in Virginia there are still a few colorful leaves on the trees, mostly due to the gorgeous Japanese maples that are sprinkled throughout town. This one in my parents&#8217; front yard keeps me craving pumpkin soup and apple cider. Its bold red color is also a great transition to Christmastime, making the Japanese maple the perfect early December tree!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/06/the-last-colors-of-fall/feed/</wfw:commentRss>

		<slash:comments>6</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wedding album for Mae and Robby</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/02/wedding-album-for-mae-and-robby/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/02/wedding-album-for-mae-and-robby/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2010 00:43:00 +0000</pubDate>

		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[albums]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fine art book]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[products]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[san francisco]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/02/wedding-album-for-mae-and-robby/</guid>

		<description><![CDATA[
It&#8217;s album season!  My clients&#8217; album orders have been coming in over the last several weeks, and it&#8217;s always fun to receive the finished books in the mail.  This one arrived today, and it&#8217;s gorgeous!  Mae and Robby got married in San Francisco, with a reception at the Cliff House, on the [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435938_xHzBT-O.jpg"></p>
<p>It&#8217;s album season!  My clients&#8217; album orders have been coming in over the last several weeks, and it&#8217;s always fun to receive the finished books in the mail.  This one arrived today, and it&#8217;s gorgeous!  Mae and Robby got married in San Francisco, with a reception at the Cliff House, on the Pacific coast.  I love this album of their beautiful wedding!</p>
<p>Mae and Robby ordered a 9&#215;12 horizontal Fine Art Book, which is one of my favorite products and sizes that I offer.  The book is contemporary and sleek, with vivid colors and slightly textured, matte pages. </p>
<p><span id="more-1922"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435788_YeftN-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435951_zskTb-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435937_NYGoz-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435952_UVCsX-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435905_Vtt2R-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435910_GtSm3-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435828_mDDJG-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435821_EHdCd-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435815_jettQ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435790_di52F-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112435810_idt2o-O.jpg"></p>
<p>Here are the layouts from the book:</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517359_qx4Rt-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517455_4CrkQ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517388_9uMfQ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517396_hCfAN-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517412_tQW2D-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517456_JWhok-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517433_9Hupq-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517431_y2vE7-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517435_5s4mD-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517445_vjAVS-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517460_nGdan-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517457_SMMA2-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517470_NYHBP-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517480_8kn8c-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517486_DCGLi-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517490_jq6N9-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517504_hM8WN-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517503_FupNF-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517510_F677j-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517541_P5NNZ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1112517525_himsC-O.jpg"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/02/wedding-album-for-mae-and-robby/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>33</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behind the scenes: 2010, part 2</title>

		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/01/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-2/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/01/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-2/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[behind the scenes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[friends]]></category>

		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/01/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-2/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Stephanie, Baby-to-be, and me, reaping the benefits of our wedding photo booth
Yesterday I posted Part 1 of my annual Behind the Scenes photos.  Here&#8217;s the second half!  As the year went on, my belly got bigger, my morning sickness got smaller, and my full wedding schedule marched on.  Some of my good [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963415_CqHjz-O-2.jpg"><br />
Stephanie, Baby-to-be, and me, reaping the benefits of our wedding photo booth</p>
<p>Yesterday I posted <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/30/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-1/">Part 1 of my annual Behind the Scenes photos</a>.  Here&#8217;s the second half!  As the year went on, my belly got bigger, my morning sickness got smaller, and my full wedding schedule marched on.  Some of my good friends second shot with me, and as you can see above, much hilarity resulted.</p>
<p><span id="more-1916"></span><br />
<img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963121_XcWf3-O.jpg"><br />
In August, Lauren and Brett were greeted by a double rainbow after their ceremony.  I grabbed this quick self-portrait after taking <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/979891567_XmCkp-O-1.jpg">this beautiful one of Lauren and Brett</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963138_yXap4-O.jpg"><br />
Later that night, I climbed a ladder to capture the essence of their <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/979891856_8G98u-O.jpg">stylish, outdoor reception downtown</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963130_2FgJf-O.jpg"><br />
At the end of the night, Brett gave me a print of the painting he did of <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/904838279_xLaRL-O.jpg">one of their engagement portraits</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963151_czZqQ-O.jpg"><br />
Later in August, Mike and I traveled to Beaver Creek for Adriana and Brian&#8217;s wedding.  We scoped out the location together early in the day.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1111220767_xboo6-O.gif"><br />
One of my frequently-used tricks is to have everyone behind me dance to entertain the children I photograph.  I love how Mike got this series of the dancers!  It almost always works, but one of the girls <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1111220862_9jVsx-O.jpg">gave only a half smile no matter what they did</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963184_XajML-O.jpg"><br />
I was starting to look quite pregnant by this point.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963176_VJA8m-O.jpg"><br />
I grabbed a quick self-portrait of Mike and me during the ceremony.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963205_22nPw-O.jpg"><br />
<a href="http://www.clickphotography.net">Tamera</a> took this picture of me and my belly at Erin and Paul&#8217;s Labor Day wedding.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963211_fJbR8-O.jpg"><br />
Erin and Paul had a photo booth, so of course Tamera and I had to play in it!  I love how Erin jumped in for the final picture.  (photo by <a href="http://www.booth66.com">Booth 66</a>)</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963220_3HNy6-O.jpg"><br />
<a href="http://www.stephaniebrauer.com">Stephanie</a> and me at Susan and Alex&#8217;s wedding the next day.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963230_9zvgb-O.jpg"><br />
Stephanie, looking cute.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963251_rkzUm-O.jpg"><br />
Stephanie and I traveled to Breckenridge the following weekend for Haley and Michael&#8217;s wedding.  I brought the baby along for the ride.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963257_2pNGF-O.jpg"><br />
Stephanie took these pictures of me before the wedding, as we were scoping out portrait locations.  We later took Haley and Michael back to this spot for this beautiful <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1026987419_E7juJ-O.jpg">portrait in the fall foliage</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963264_V4rQt-O.jpg"><br />
Haley&#8217;s <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1026987355_Rn5Sy-O.jpg">dog Pierre</a> was a guest at the wedding, and Stephanie got to hold him during the portraits.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963276_Murca-O.jpg"><br />
Stephanie and me at the reception that night.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963283_xfX9q-O.jpg"><br />
It was another great dance party.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1111220668_HUw98-O.jpg"><br />
At the end of the night, we met up with Mike at a bar in Breckenridge.  This is what I look like when the adrenaline wears off after a long day of shooting at high altitude while six months pregnant.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963297_GDVvV-O.jpg"><br />
In early October, Mike and I flew off to Orlando for Liz and Jeremy&#8217;s wedding.  This is what I was looking like at that point.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963304_tdo7v-O.jpg"><br />
Liz&#8217;s grandmother flirted with Mike during the family portraits.  I wanted to jump in and fight for my man, but she was so darn sweet that I let her get away with it.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963310_rGNL4-O.jpg"><br />
Mike is always really cute with kids.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963317_yuPFn-O.jpg"><br />
At six months pregnant, I couldn&#8217;t lie on my stomach any more, but that didn&#8217;t stop me from rolling around on the ground.  Ok, I lay on my stomach a little, too &#8211; I had to for <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1036977701_3pemt-O-3.jpg">this picture</a>.  The baby didn&#8217;t mind, but Mike wasn&#8217;t so sure.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963322_zPU7h-O.jpg"><br />
In November, I had already moved to Virginia, but I traveled back to Denver for Tracy and John&#8217;s wedding. Here Tamera and I are taking the bride and groom&#8217;s portraits on the 16th Street Mall.  Our low perspectives enabled us to eliminate some of the crowds of people in the background, to get portraits <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042497_KjSKi-O.jpg">like this</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963335_unnYs-O.jpg"><br />
I thought my winter coat would conceal my belly a little, but nope, it was sticking out loud and clear!</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963345_uGR85-O.jpg"><br />
Here&#8217;s a cute one of Tamera having fun during the portrait shoot!</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963361_USfTs-O.jpg"><br />
Later in the night, I had Stephanie sit on a cold bench while I did some lighting tests.  Then Tracy and John stepped in for <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042597_kqnFg-O.jpg">this portrait</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963381_xdpGG-O.jpg"><br />
A wedding gelato bar is a pregnant photographer&#8217;s dream come true.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963380_2Hqob-O.jpg"><br />
I like this cute series of Tamera in the <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/16/tracy-and-john-wedding-photo-booth-madness/">photo booth</a>&#8230;</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963384_y2m46-O.jpg"><br />
&#8230; cute!</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963390_bNfqS-O.jpg"><br />
Here&#8217;s a funny picture of super-pregnant me shooting the rings.  Note that I had my gelato sitting right next to me for easy access.  In this location, I took <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042733_WRarP-O.jpg">this ring shot</a> and <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042716_YmvfC-O.jpg">this one</a>.  Both were lit with my on-camera flash bounced backward and sideways.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963397_bXPr5-O.jpg"><br />
Me and Tam in the photo booth</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963402_Fkco7-O-1.jpg"><br />
Yes, it was another great dance party!  </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963409_hFbdP-O-2.jpg"><br />
Me and baby at the end of the night.  I look pretty huge here, but it was three weeks ago, so I&#8217;m even bigger now!  I&#8217;m due in about four weeks, so stay tuned!</p>
<p>I&#8217;d like to take a moment to give a huge thank you to everyone who made 2010 such a success for me. </p>
<p>To Mike, Stephanie, Tamera, Jesse, David, Amber, and JoEllen: I am so lucky to have had you share your talent, support, and friendship throughout the year.  I couldn&#8217;t have done it without you.</p>
<p>To my clients: Thank you for trusting me and inviting me into your lives.  It&#8217;s been such a pleasure getting to know you and your families, and I hope you&#8217;ll love the photos for many years to come.  And thanks for the great dance music and cake.</p>
<p>To my baby: We did it, little guy.  You&#8217;ve already been to more weddings than most people attend in a lifetime, and your lifetime hasn&#8217;t even begun yet. Thank you for being healthy and strong, and helping me to be the same.  But mostly I thank you just for being there.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/12/01/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>16</slash:comments>

		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behind the scenes: 2010, part 1</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/30/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-1/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/30/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-1/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>

				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[behind the scenes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[friends]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/30/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-1/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Yours truly, doing the Cupid Shuffle at Sarah and Mike&#8217;s wedding
At the end of every wedding season, I post a series of photos of us in action at weddings.  I love going through all the pictures and seeing how much fun I had throughout the year.  2010 was particularly memorable, because it was [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963098_Yruj3-O.jpg"><br />
Yours truly, doing the Cupid Shuffle at Sarah and Mike&#8217;s wedding</p>
<p>At the end of every wedding season, I post a series of photos of us in action at weddings.  I love going through all the pictures and seeing how much fun I had throughout the year.  2010 was particularly memorable, because it was my busiest year ever, and because I&#8217;ve been pregnant for most of it.  The pregnancy didn&#8217;t slow me down.  Neither did a sprained ankle &#8211; in this picture, I had sprained it about two hours earlier, but the wedding day adrenaline made the dance floor as irresistible to me as always.</p>
<p>For photos from previous years, scroll through the blog posts <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/?tag=behind-the-scenes">here</a>.</p>
<p>Here are pictures from the first half of 2010!  Some of these photos may look familiar, because I&#8217;ve shared a few of them in posts about my pregnancy.  But most are new.  Pictures from the second half of the year will come later this week. <img src='http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif' alt=':)' class='wp-smiley' /> </p>
<p><span id="more-1909"></span><br />
<img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962725_F4mNA-O.jpg"><br />
In January, I had the incredible honor of photographing <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/01/30/birth-photography-the-birth-of-ellie/">the birth of baby Ellie</a>.  Afterward, I had a chance to hold the beautiful little girl.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962732_fsrhj-O.jpg"><br />
Here I am with baby Ellie and her mom, <a href="http://www.realphotography.com">Traci</a>.  Traci had given birth about an hour earlier and looked amazing.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962739_gkbou-O.jpg"><br />
In March, I got ambushed by guests at a wedding in Vail.  Obviously I wouldn&#8217;t have wanted to be rude by turning down the nice gentlemen.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962795_fqxZG-O.jpg"><br />
In April, Mike and I headed to Lake Tahoe for Amanda and Stephen&#8217;s wedding. This picture cracks me up, because I have a stunning lake to use for portrait backdrops, but I am posing the bride and groom under this ugly staircase.  But they trusted me, which enabled me to get some soft light for close-ups like <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/843966185_zMDAX-O.jpg">this one</a>.  Don&#8217;t worry, we still took lots of scenic portraits <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/843965960_NQGjP-O-1.jpg">like this</a>. </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962757_x2ybA-O.jpg"><br />
Here&#8217;s Mike, getting a cool angle of Amanda&#8217;s veil.  You&#8217;ll see that &#8220;rolling on the ground&#8221; is a common theme in these behind-the-scenes pictures.  The best angles aren&#8217;t always at eye level.  <img src='http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif' alt=':)' class='wp-smiley' /> </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962759_zfJJC-O.jpg"><br />
Mike and me, enjoying beautiful Lake Tahoe.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962774_Z5pvB-O.jpg"><br />
One of my favorite photo shoots of the year was <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/05/05/colorado-engagement-portraits-carrie-and-pete/">Carrie and Pete&#8217;s engagement session</a>.  I&#8217;d never done a photo shoot on a farm before, so I was surprised/delighted/freaked when Chuck the cow followed me around for several of the pictures.  She was right behind me for a while, so at one point I turned the camera around to capture the hilarity of the situation.  The look on my face here says it all!</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962777_iGUJt-O.jpg"><br />
In May, I traveled to England to photograph <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/06/01/ali-and-howard-wedding-at-st-audries-park-in-england/">Ali and Howard&#8217;s wedding</a>.  This getting ready photo was a first for me &#8211; the handsome best man getting dressed is my husband Mike!</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962785_aXdRh-O.jpg"><br />
Check out this cool English wedding venue!  They don&#8217;t make &#8216;em like that in the States.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962804_BiSCi-O.jpg"><br />
My friend <a href="http://www.openleafimages.com/">David Pearce</a> drove all the way from Kent to help with with this wedding.  I see that even well-mannered Brits aren&#8217;t afraid to roll on the ground at a wedding!</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962810_ymGt7-O.jpg"><br />
Of course the ground is the only place to get an adorable picture <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/887077908_J8Ho5-O.jpg">like this one</a> of Ali and Howard&#8217;s son, William.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962817_dhRFC-O.jpg"><br />
Howard was the best man in our wedding and is like a brother to Mike, so now Ali is family, too.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962830_AZbYc-O.jpg"><br />
The two best men and their ladies.  Unfortunately I was wearing my photo garb instead of a cute dress like Rosie&#8217;s.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962836_8NoSZ-O.jpg"><br />
During Mike&#8217;s best man speech, he said some wonderfully romantic things about being married to me.  Bride Ali took my camera away from me so I could stop and enjoy the moment. <img src='http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif' alt=':)' class='wp-smiley' /> </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962854_tYDRM-O.jpg"><br />
Mike likes to remind me that not all old, pretty buildings in England are castles.  I don&#8217;t care what he says&#8230; <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/887077496_bs4L4-O.jpg">this was a castle</a> to me.  </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962857_ZEaNx-O.jpg"><br />
In June I photographed a backyard wedding at Carissa and Adam&#8217;s farm in Colorado.  Since it took place at their house, their affectionate cat was a part of the day.  </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962869_64m7t-O.jpg"><br />
Anyone who knows me knows that I can&#8217;t resist a cat.  Especially a friendly black cat!</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962874_J2vuP-O.jpg"><br />
Later that month, <a href="http://www.jessestarrphotography.com/">Jesse Starr</a> began shooting with me.  He has such a great way with kids!</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962887_WzKpz-O.jpg"><br />
This year I photographed the weddings of several photographers, including Vie.  I walked into a room before the wedding and found Vie and Jesse talking shop. It&#8217;s hard to stop being a photographer on your wedding day!  </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962893_KEppe-O.jpg"><br />
I have no clue what Vie was doing back there, but I&#8217;m sure it made Nichole laugh, and was therefore perfect.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962899_aGqxG-O.jpg"><br />
By late June, I was three months pregnant, and my stomach was starting to pooch out a little bit.  I was wearing Sea-Bands to help with the morning sickness.  I&#8217;m not sure if they worked, but I got through all the weddings just fine, thank goodness.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962911_rSSpa-O.jpg"><br />
I loved the texture of Emma&#8217;s gown, especially when the light would shine through it.  (Edited to add: <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1110097377_CSPVe-O.jpg">here&#8217;s the picture I was taking</a>.)</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962916_CSgd5-O.jpg"><br />
Here I am at the Air Force Academy Chapel, taking <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/926701004_PUjms-O.jpg">this picture of Emma and Kyle</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962925_ChoZG-O.jpg"><br />
Stephanie caught this picture of me grinning in response to Emma and Kyle&#8217;s <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/926701088_X8PvJ-O.jpg">adorable strawberry cake topper</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962929_Uu7it-O.jpg"><br />
<a href="http://www.stephaniebrauer.com">Stephanie Brauer</a> and me</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962934_cJRAd-O.jpg"><br />
When Emma&#8217;s mother found out that I was pregnant at the end of the day, she sent me home with a whole box full of desserts.  I was so happy that I asked the lady at the Broadmoor Hotel&#8217;s front desk to take a picture.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962942_j6H2A-O.jpg"><br />
In early July, I could still lie on my stomach, which was a great perspective for <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/927484909_PrfaX-O.jpg">this photo of Jamie</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962952_diewY-O.jpg"><br />
Just another day in Colorado paradise.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962962_3UtVY-O.jpg"><br />
I like to make myself useful.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962967_L9W4o-O.jpg"><br />
I look at this picture now and can&#8217;t believe that I thought my stomach was sticking out a lot then.  I look like a waddling watermelon these days.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109962975_YzTdB-O.jpg"><br />
Here I am, making myself useful again.  I really should ask a florist to teach me how to fasten boutonnieres the right way.  I just taught myself one day, in response to frequent requests for help.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963001_MvdwV-O.jpg"><br />
Jesse and me on the Keystone gondola, on our way to a wedding.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963007_LMrvA-O.jpg"><br />
With Kasey and Dave at the top of the mountain in Keystone, setting up <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/949742680_W2opd-O-1.jpg">this picture</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963018_5gJmL-O.jpg"><br />
The life of a traveling photographer sounds more glamorous than it is.  Here I am, shooting while in a toilet stall.  <img src='http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_wink.gif' alt=';-)' class='wp-smiley' /> </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963013_2qHHf-O.jpg"><br />
With Chris and Dave, at the top of the mountain in Keystone, setting up <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/950783538_3Kpme-O.jpg">this picture</a>.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963021_ZxLki-O.jpg"><br />
By late July, I was definitely showing.  </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963027_cXN6p-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963047_Vt5QG-O.jpg"><br />
In early August, bride Sarah smuggled <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/968223126_Yy94F-O.jpg">her cat into the church</a> while they were getting ready.  As I mentioned earlier, I can&#8217;t resist a cute cat.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963064_mm92L-O.jpg"><br />
After the ceremony, we took Sarah and Mike to the Garden of the Gods to take scenic portraits like <a href="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/968223190_Y2ewk-O.jpg">this one</a>.  It was on these rocks that I fell and sprained my ankle.  I stood up, kept shooting, and then called Mike from the car on the way to the reception. </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963073_oL7pW-O.jpg"><br />
During the meal, I sat down with an ice pack and laughed it all off while waiting for Mike.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963084_WUqWS-O.jpg"><br />
Mike hurried over with Tylenol and ankle braces.  </p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963093_Leaqp-O.jpg"><br />
The ankle braces, combined with the adrenaline rush of the wedding, kept me comfortably on my feet the rest of the night.  As I mentioned earlier, the wedding was so much fun that I even danced.</p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1109963107_jTMVi-O.jpg"><br />
4.5 months pregnant.</p>
<p>Stay tuned for Part 2 of my behind the scenes photos!</p>
]]></content:encoded>

			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/30/behind-the-scenes-2010-part-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>27</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tracy and John: Magnolia Hotel wedding in downtown Denver</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/18/tracy-and-john-magnolia-hotel-wedding-in-downtown-denver/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/18/tracy-and-john-magnolia-hotel-wedding-in-downtown-denver/#comments</comments>

		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 22:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[denver]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/18/tracy-and-john-magnolia-hotel-wedding-in-downtown-denver/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Tracy and John
Magnolia Hotel
Denver, Colorado
November 13, 2010
Last weekend I traveled back to Colorado to photograph the wedding of Tracy and John in downtown Denver.  I loved their wedding&#8217;s chic, urban style, which was made even better by their willingness to walk around in the cold for some portraits in the city!  Tracy is [...]]]></description>

			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="Denver wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042322_Re5oB-O.jpg"><br />
Tracy and John<br />
Magnolia Hotel<br />
Denver, Colorado<br />
November 13, 2010</p>
<p>Last weekend I traveled back to Colorado to photograph the wedding of Tracy and John in downtown Denver.  I loved their wedding&#8217;s chic, urban style, which was made even better by their willingness to walk around in the cold for some portraits in the city!  Tracy is a talented <a href="http://www.tracycarolyn.com/">wedding photographer</a> herself, so it was an honor for her to ask me to photograph her own wedding.  You might remember her and John from their <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/08/26/tracy-and-john-engagement-portraits-in-downtown-denver/">engagement portraits</a> in Denver last summer. </p>
<p>This was my last wedding before my maternity leave, and it was certainly a great one to end my season.  My good friends and talented colleagues, <a href="http://www.clickphotography.net">Tamera Goldsmith</a> and <a href="http://www.stephaniebrauer.com">Stephanie Brauer</a> photographed this wedding with me.  Not only are they great photographers, but they are also a ton of fun to work with.  The photos posted here were taken by all three of us.  Thanks, Tam and Steph!  </p>
<p><span id="more-1901"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042348_sm6kx-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Blue earrings for wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042362_wEN5E-O.jpg"><br />
Tracy&#8217;s blue jewelry were a perfect match for her eyes.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Bride with halter dress" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042391_UAXQd-O-2.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042380_2GZ3d-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042390_rPhnc-O.jpg"><br />
John carried his father&#8217;s heirloom pocket watch.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042410_sJcC3-O.jpg"><br />
Tracy and John saw each other before the wedding, and then spent some time walking around the 16th Street Mall together.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042421_6v8z5-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042426_uB6Wc-O.jpg"><br />
The sun sets so early these days!</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Green and white bridal bouquet" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042469_AxPJN-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042452_ZQEDb-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042460_othp4-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Groom in gray suit" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042473_4CZaF-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042479_RHztt-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Denver wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042492_SQzHP-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Denver wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042497_KjSKi-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Downtown Denver wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042510_koPj4-O.jpg"><br />
Their maid of honor and best man joined them for some pictures along the 16th Street Mall.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Magnolia hotel wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042527_4Ur9A-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Magnolia hotel wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042556_PWAeL-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Magnolia hotel wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042547_aTkVa-O.jpg"><br />
Tracy and John got married under a canopy of orange and blue lanterns.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Magnolia hotel wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042555_CCSk4-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042573_eRaa2-O.jpg"><br />
The newlyweds, immediately after the ceremony</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042607_tptEY-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Urban wedding portraits" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042580_vhQnr-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="urban wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042597_kqnFg-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Night time wedding pictures" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042579_eqpf4-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Urban wedding pictures" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042601_oGG7M-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Magnolia Hotel wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042612_UFiSp-O.jpg"><br />
John and his friends asked for a Reservoir Dogs shot in the alley&#8230;</p>
<p><img border="1"  alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042627_xiEg9-O.jpg"><br />
&#8230; then I cracked up when they busted out into the Sharks and Jets from West Side Story!</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042639_hGrvv-O.jpg"><br />
I was quite literally rolling on the ground laughing here.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Magnolia Hotel wedding" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042653_DGbMs-O.jpg"><br />
The Magnolia Hotel is a stylish and contemporary venue, with great little seating areas like these.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042681_qUiYn-O.jpg"><br />
During the toasts</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042677_Dgnqd-O.jpg"><br />
I had no idea that John and Tracy were such great dancers!  Their first dance was a swing routine that thrilled us all.</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042691_hgpEa-O.jpg"><br />
John dancing with his mother</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042701_ycCYL-O.jpg"><br />
All the ladies wanted to dance with John.  He had some serious moves!</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042768_Gj4oH-O.jpg"><br />
John&#8217;s niece</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="Blue wedding rings" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042733_WRarP-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1096042716_YmvfC-O.jpg"></p>
<p>Photographer: <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com">Charlotte Geary</a><br />
Second photographer: <a href="http://www.clickphotography.net">Tamera Goldsmith</a><br />
Second photographer: <a href="http://www.stephaniebrauer.com">Stephanie Brauer</a><br />
Venue: <a href="">Magnolia Hotel</a><br />
Coordinators: Maryann and Danielle of <a href="">Something Classic Events</a><br />
DJ: Jeremy of <a href="http://www.dj-center-stage-entertainment.com/">Center Stage Entertainment</a><br />
Florist: <a href="http://www.theperfectpetal.com/">The Perfect Petal</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/18/tracy-and-john-magnolia-hotel-wedding-in-downtown-denver/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>34</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tracy and John: Wedding photo booth madness!</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/16/tracy-and-john-wedding-photo-booth-madness/</link>

		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/16/tracy-and-john-wedding-photo-booth-madness/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weddings]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/17/tracy-and-john-wedding-photo-booth-madness/</guid>

		<description><![CDATA[
Tracy and John&#8217;s photo booth
November 13, 2010
On Saturday I photographed a really fun wedding in downtown Denver.  Those photos are coming soon, but first I wanted to share the results of my first wedding photo booth!  We set up a portrait station at the reception, and my good friend and second shooter extraordinaire, [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094095806_ZFdcj-O.jpg"><br />
Tracy and John&#8217;s photo booth<br />
November 13, 2010</p>
<p>On Saturday I photographed a really fun wedding in downtown Denver.  Those photos are coming soon, but first I wanted to share the results of my first wedding photo booth!  We set up a portrait station at the reception, and my good friend and second shooter extraordinaire, <a href="http://www.clickphotography.net">Tamera Goldsmith</a>, operated it throughout the party.  The results are fantastic!  I definitely want to offer photo booths at future weddings!</p>
<p><span id="more-1897"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034679_cRXVZ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034772_PH9VE-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034762_aBkpp-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034858_hm5Vm-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034831_QqqPY-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034822_E6Rng-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034870_uhyaU-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034898_Lbgvj-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034914_PqYPi-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034941_Z4i5z-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094035086_nJCEZ-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094034967_NpU3q-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/1094035009_CKRDf-O.jpg"></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/16/tracy-and-john-wedding-photo-booth-madness/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>14</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>We&#8217;ve moved! I&#8217;m a Washington DC photographer now!</title>

		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/06/weve-moved-im-a-washington-dc-photographer-now/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/06/weve-moved-im-a-washington-dc-photographer-now/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/06/weve-moved-im-a-washington-dc-photographer-now/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We&#8217;ve arrived in DC!  After several hectic weeks of preparing to move and then driving cross-country, we&#8217;re now getting settled in Northern Virginia.  I will be getting back to work on Monday, and I appreciate everyone&#8217;s patience during this past week.  
I will be available for DC-area weddings and portraits starting in [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;ve arrived in DC!  After several hectic weeks of preparing to move and then driving cross-country, we&#8217;re now getting settled in Northern Virginia.  I will be getting back to work on Monday, and I appreciate everyone&#8217;s patience during this past week.  </p>
<p>I will be available for DC-area weddings and portraits starting in May, after my maternity leave. I will no longer be taking Colorado portrait commissions.  As always, I&#8217;m willing to travel anywhere for weddings, including Colorado, but travel fees will apply.</p>
<p>I had intended to blog a series of posts about what I&#8217;ll miss most about Colorado, but I&#8217;ve been so swamped that I haven&#8217;t had the time.  Maybe I&#8217;ll do them later, or maybe I&#8217;ll post photos of why I&#8217;m glad to be in DC.  Or maybe I&#8217;ll rest instead!  I&#8217;m not sure yet. <img src='http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif' alt=':)' class='wp-smiley' /> </p>
<p>Our next step is to find a new home!  Wish us luck&#8230; this process is overwhelming!  In the meanwhile we are settling comfortably at our temporary address in Annandale, Virginia.  We hope to find the right home very soon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/11/06/weve-moved-im-a-washington-dc-photographer-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>26</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>

		<title>What I&#8217;ll Miss About Colorado: Red Rock Canyon Open Space</title>
		<link>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/10/18/what-ill-miss-about-colorado-red-rock-canyon-open-space/</link>
		<comments>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/10/18/what-ill-miss-about-colorado-red-rock-canyon-open-space/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>charlottegeary</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All posts]]></category>

		<category><![CDATA[colorado]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[colorado springs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[my family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[personal photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[red rock canyon]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/10/18/what-ill-miss-about-colorado-red-rock-canyon-open-space/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[
Ally in Red Rock Canyon
Colorado Springs, CO
We always knew this time would come, but it&#8217;s hard to believe that it&#8217;s finally here.  We&#8217;re actually leaving our beloved Colorado.  When Mike and I moved here in 2004, we had planned to stay only three years or so before returning to live closer to our [...]]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="Red Rock Canyon Open Space" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/558242440_pXtfq-O.jpg"><br />
Ally in Red Rock Canyon<br />
Colorado Springs, CO</p>
<p>We always knew this time would come, but it&#8217;s hard to believe that it&#8217;s finally here.  We&#8217;re actually leaving our beloved Colorado.  When Mike and I moved here in 2004, we had planned to stay only three years or so before returning to live closer to our families.  Six years later, we are in love with this gorgeous state and sad to be leaving.  But we&#8217;ve always wanted to be surrounded by family when we have children, and that time has come.  As much as we&#8217;re looking forward to all the big changes ahead of us, we&#8217;re also going to miss Colorado dreadfully.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ll be leaving in just a couple weeks.  In the meanwhile, I thought I&#8217;d put together a series of blog posts about some of the things that I&#8217;ll miss most about Colorado.  First and foremost, I&#8217;ll miss my friends here.  Colorado has such wonderful people, and it will be hard to say goodbye.  I&#8217;m especially grateful to all my photographer friends for welcoming me into their community when I moved here, and for years of friendship and support.  But because I&#8217;m afraid that I&#8217;ll exclude someone, I won&#8217;t post photos of the friends that I&#8217;ll miss the most.  You all know who you are, and I&#8217;m going to miss you so much. </p>
<p>Instead, I&#8217;m going to start with photos of a place that has been very special to Mike and me over the years &#8212; Red Rock Canyon Open Space in Colorado Springs.  This enormous park is great for hiking, and we live only two blocks from one of the trailheads.  Over the years, it has been our favorite place to walk the dog, enjoy nature, and spend time together.  We&#8217;ve been so fortunate to have a place like this as our backyard, and we&#8217;ve never taken it for granted.  As much as we love the DC area, we know we&#8217;ll never have a place anything like Red Rock Canyon after we move.</p>
<p>Red Rock Canyon has also been a great place for my portrait photography.  You can see some of my photo shoots from the canyon <a href="http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/?tag=red-rock-canyon">HERE</a>.</p>
<p><span id="more-1884"></span></p>
<p align="center"><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/424071021_5Pi8b-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/558242334_K8EH4-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/159308660-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/424070913_bGtjr-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/558242684_syB9a-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/221554852-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/558242386_wXbA7-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/163053434-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/430033143_Q8YcE-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/163053471-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/163053477-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/558242453_niqZ6-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/159308561-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/221554780-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/430033080_W4f9e-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/430033193_YeRjp-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/221554679-O.jpg"><br />
My parents</p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/221554716-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/159308537-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/736127093_fg6qM-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/736105650_4QyGm-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/736105680_rZyMo-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/714490095_mRhsa-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/714490039_QTKT4-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://charlottegeary.smugmug.com/photos/714490252_sVLgq-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/736105702_kMRM6-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/736105663_eJ32R-O.jpg"></p>
<p><img border="1" alt="" src="http://galleries.charlottegeary.com/photos/736105671_zhzQm-O.jpg"></p>
]]></content:encoded>

			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.charlottegeary.com/blog/2010/10/18/what-ill-miss-about-colorado-red-rock-canyon-open-space/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>11</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
